[{"question" : "What is my favorite color? ($0.50)", "answer" : "orange", "reward" : 0.50}, 
{"question" : "What is the the name of the cryptocurrency you earn by correctly answering questions? ($1.07)", "answer" : "monero", "reward" : 1.07},
{"question" : "What is the first name of the CEO of Google? ($0.69)", "answer" : "sundar", "reward" : 0.69},
{"question" : "What year was Youtube founded? ($0.15)", "answer" : "2005", "reward" : 0.15},
{"question" : "How many tentacles does an octopus have? ($0.15)", "answer" : "8", "reward" : 0.15},
{"question" : "What is the most popular Tiktoker's first name? ($0.20)", "answer" : "charli", "reward" : 0.20},
{"question" : "Who is the main character in Dragon Ball Z? ($0.50)", "answer" : "goku", "reward" : 0.50},
{"question" : "What year did SpongeBob first air? ($0.75)", "answer" : "1999", "reward" : 0.75},
{"question" : "What company owns Xbox? ($0.50)", "answer" : "microsoft", "reward" : 0.50},
{"question" : "What company owns Instagram? ($0.55)", "answer" : "facebook", "reward" : 0.55},
{"question" : "How do people from New York say 'cold'? ($2.00)", "answer" : "brick", "reward" : 2.00},
{"question" : "How do people from Texas say 'hi'? ($1.00)", "answer" : "howdy", "reward" : 1.00},
{"question" : "What year was GTA 5 released? ($0.75)", "answer" : "2013", "reward" : 0.75},
{"question" : "What is the capital of New York? ($1.25)", "answer" : "albany", "reward" : 1.25},
{"question" : "What is the capital of India? ($1.25)", "answer" : "new delhi", "reward" : 1.25},
{"question" : "What is the most populated country in Africa? ($0.55)", "answer" : "nigeria", "reward" : 0.55},
{"question" : "How many weeks are there in a year? ($1.00)", "answer" : "52", "reward" : 1.00},
{"question" : "What is the capital of Canada? ($0.50)", "answer" : "ottawa", "reward" : 0.50},
{"question" : "How many weeks are there in a year? ($0.10)", "answer" : "52", "reward" : 0.10},
{"question" : "What is the second largest state in the US? ($0.69)", "answer" : "texas", "reward" : 0.69},
{"question" : "What is the largest state in the US? ($0.69)", "answer" : "alaska", "reward" : 0.69},
{"question" : "What is the most populous city in the world? ($0.50)", "answer" : "tokyo", "reward" : 0.50},
{"question" : "What is the 7th planet in our solar system? ($0.60)", "answer" : "uranus", "reward" : 0.60},
{"question" : "What is The Rock's first name? ($0.30)", "answer" : "dwayne", "reward" : 0.30},
{"question" : "What is Elon Musk's last name? ($0.01)", "answer" : "musk", "reward" : 0.01}]
